And so I'm just going to show the line of force now
そして、今から力の線を示すだけです。
to go from the periphery to the base of the skull,
末梢から頭蓋底へ向かうために、
to finally balance the face in relation to the brain.
最終的に顔と脳のバランスを取るために。
Neurocranium and viscerocranium articulate in a certain way on
神経頭蓋と内臓頭蓋は、ある意味で
this sphenobasilar symphysis.
この蝶形後頭軟骨結合で関節を形成しています。
And so I can't not treat both together, if you will.
だから、両方を一緒に扱わないわけにはいかない、もしそうしたいなら。
I have to take it as one idea.
私はそれを一つのアイデアとして捉えなければなりません。
At the same time, I have the whole nervous system that I treat in relation to everything.
同時に、私はすべての神経系を全体として扱っています。
visceral system and I'm just going to rebalance them. The baby goes from the umbilical
内臓系と、私はそれらを単に再調整するつもりです。赤ちゃんはへそから
to
口のレベルへ。
the oral level. He must be able to bring all the information back to
すべての情報を口のレベルに持ち帰ることができなければなりません。
the mouth.
口のレベルに。
If you observe a baby who is not gathering himself, be careful, you
もし、まとまらない赤ちゃんを見たら、注意してください。
must help him to find
彼が自分自身でまとまるのを助ける必要があります。
his midline.
彼の正中線へ。
A child, in fact, becomes extraordinary.
子供は、実際、並外れた存在になります。
oral. It's a survival zone, he has to bring everything to his mouth
口の。それは生存の領域であり、彼はすべてを口に持ち帰らなければなりません。
and so he likes in fact
だから、彼は実際には
to be given a point of support, whether in a sitting position. For a very small baby,
支えを与えられることを好みます。座っている姿勢でも。非常に小さな赤ちゃんの場合、
I rarely treat
私は頭蓋骨を治療することはめったにありません。
the cranium. First I treat the pelvis, the
まず骨盤、内臓を治療します。
viscera. I rarely go to the cranium. If I
内臓。私はめったに頭蓋骨に行きません。もし私が
go to the cranium, I give a point of support at the jaw, but I rarely touch the head.
頭蓋骨に行くなら、顎のレベルで支えを与えますが、頭にはめったに触れません。
You shouldn't go too far into that right away.
すぐにそこに行き過ぎてはいけません。
It's still very fragile, you see.
まだ非常に壊れやすいのです。
On the other hand, you have to indicate certain concepts a little bit.
しかし、いくつかの概念を示す必要があります。
A child is first and foremost a belly.
子供はまずお腹です。
If you're not fair, he'll show you very quickly.
もしあなたが正しくなければ、彼はすぐにそれを示すでしょう。
Follow that, you see.
それに従ってください。
First, relax the pelvis well, relax the sacrum well, relax the digestive area well.
まず、骨盤をよく緩め、仙骨をよく緩め、消化器系をよく緩めます。
digestive.
消化器系を。
And if necessary, relax the mediastinum well.
そして、必要であれば、縦隔をよく緩めます。
And if you have to go to the cranium, work.
そして、頭蓋骨に行く必要があるなら、非常に軽く作業してください。
very, very lightly. I'm going to take the dural sheath here, a middle dural sheath,
非常に軽く作業してください。私はここで硬膜鞘、中硬膜鞘を取ります。
which I'm going to take like this. The lighter you touch, the deeper you go.
このように取ります。軽く触れるほど、深部に入り込みます。
I let the anatomy visualize itself in my body. As
私は解剖学が私の体の中で視覚化されるのを許します。
it's a densification a little
それは少し異なる濃密化なので、
different, it means it's a slightly stronger electric field. It's
それは少し強い電場を意味します。それは硬膜鞘なので。
a dural sheath so
それは硬膜鞘なので。
I touch first from the periphery, there, there, she can feel as if
まず、私は周辺から触れます。そこでは、彼女は私が少し深く入っていくように感じるかもしれません。
I'm going a little deeper, maybe you can perceive that.
おそらく、あなたはそれを感じ取ることができるでしょう。
There's a very small deviation, well, deviation, meaning that it
ほんの少しのずれがあります。いや、ずれというよりは、それが私を
brings me a very small bit into torsion,
ほんの少しねじれさせているということです。
so she has a small point of support, but I saw it, so
だから、彼女には小さな支点がありますが、私はそれを見ました。だから、
I don't go in, either I go into the facial, but there I don't go, I go rather into a school.
私は入り込みません。顔面に行くか、しかしそこには行きません。むしろ、私はある学校に行きます。
biodynamic so I stay on health I don't let myself be hypnotized
生体力学的なので、私は健康に留まり、催眠術にかかりません。
by the
病変に
lesion or attracted and I stay on it I wait
引き寄せられたりせず、その場に留まり、待ちます。
but I am in the globality
しかし、私は全体性の中にいます。
I have a vision of globality that is
私は全体性のビジョンを持っています。つまり、
to say that I turn the page so if I am
ページをめくるということです。だから、もし私が突然、ある緊張や病変に
suddenly attracted to a tension, a lesion
引き寄せられたとしても、
I don't go into it.
私はそこには入り込みません。
I say, ah, I'm in my head, I say, ah, I saw you, it's good.
私は「ああ、頭の中だ」と言い、「ああ、わかったよ」と言います。
You don't look for the pulls.
あなたは引っ張るものを探しません。
No, I don't look for the pulls, I stay on health.
いいえ、私は引っ張るものを探しません。私は健康に留まります。
Not further into the lesion, but further into the depth anyway.
病変の奥深くではなく、それでも深さの奥深くへ。
Yes, there, now, I put myself on this frequency.
はい、今、私はこの周波数に合わせます。
So, I can put myself, you see, here, on a purely hair frequency.
だから、私はここ、純粋に髪の毛の周波数に合わせることができます。
There, I come back, I change, I come back to the hair.
はい、戻ります。変えて、髪の毛に戻ります。
Then, I'm going more for a frequency, different frequented qualities.
そして、私はむしろ、異なる周波数の質へと向かいます。
on the skin, there, then I'm going more for
皮膚の上で、はい、そして私はむしろ
a rather bony tissue, really I'm still
骨のような組織へと向かいます。本当に、私はまだ
skin, there, I've changed frequency, there I'm lowering the
皮膚です。はい、私は周波数を変えました。そこで、私は手を
hand a bit to feel it normally
少し下げて、通常はそれを感じるようにします。
we can perceive that something different, it's as if I was slowly entering the
何か違うものを感じ取ることができます。まるで私がゆっくりと骨に
bone
入っていくようです。
and the dura mater, it was the same thing, it's just a
そして硬膜は同じものでした。それはただの
dance
ダンスです。
at a given moment. There I put myself there, there I see and
ある時点で。私はそこに身を置きます。そこを見て、
I stay there, but I'm always in the
そこに留まります。しかし、私は常に
globality. If you ask me what my intention is, I stay on the
全体性の中にいます。もしあなたが私の意図は何だと尋ねるなら、私は
pattern of health. No, no, no,
健康のパターンに留まります。いいえ、いいえ、いいえ。
there I am in an immobility. At the same time I put myself in this line, in this
私は不動の中にいます。同時に、私はこの線、この
anatomical approach
アプローチに身を置きます。
of my line of my dural sheath, the thickening, in the globality
私の硬膜鞘の線、その肥厚の解剖学的アプローチ、全体性の中で、
while staying on
健康に
health so I don't go into a lesion so now I just wanted to
留まりながら。だから、私は病変には向かいません。だから、今、私はただ
make you feel this field here, did you perceive it?
この場の感覚を感じてほしかったのです。感じ取れましたか？
now I put myself here and there I'm going to put myself on this sheath here
さて、ここに身を置き、この鞘の上に身を置きます。
I put myself here I take the mandibular arch WAN my
ここに身を置き、下顎弓を取ります。私の
two lines meet
2本の線が
here you see at the symphysis so I'm going to wait very slowly
ここで合流します。結合部でね。だから、ゆっくりと待ちます。
connection if you want so I put myself in the form fields I
接続、もしよろしければ。だから、私は形態の場に入ります。私は
am on the
冠状縫合にいます。私は知っています。
these two lines are like arches they
これら2本の線はアーチのようで、
all meet in the public square I
すべて広場で合流します。私は
feel the area that is working and even if
働いている領域を感じます。そして、たとえ
it's very light it's heavy in depth that's biodynamics it's like
それがとても軽くても、深部では重いです。これが生体力学です。それはまるで
who works there I give her her point she will
そこで働いているかのように。私は彼女にポイントを与えます。彼女は
feel something there I will
何かを感じるでしょう。さあ、私はあなたに
describe I will help you because you don't know very well what you felt but you felt
説明します。私はあなたを助けます。なぜなら、あなたは自分が何を感じたのかよくわからないでしょうが、あなたは
something more unitary so simply coming back to that level is
より統一された何かを感じました。だから、単にそのレベルに戻るだけです。それは
the system there
システムです。さあ。
I was just on another level it's different you may have
私は別のレベルにいました。それは違います。あなたは
played on thymic planes so that
胸腺の平面で遊ぶことができます。だから、それは
These are also ancient correspondences on the levels of anterior lines.
これは、以前の線レベルにおける古い対応でもあります。
We'll see with Mademoiselle if we can help her a little bit on one level.
お嬢さんの場合、少しでも助けられるかどうか見てみましょう。
She has still recorded some things in her hard drive.
彼女はやはり、ハードディスクにいくつかのことを記録しています。
We'll see here.
ここで見てみましょう。
I'm going to try to make you feel a concentration of time.
時間の集中を感じていただけるように努めます。
She still has a good concentration here.
彼女はやはり、ここに素晴らしい集中力を持っています。
It's not a knot.
それは結び目ではありません。
it's a bit even just I'm going to clear it
少し、いや、ただ、私は取り除きます。
otherwise that's an old memory
そうでなければ、それは記憶です。
old
古い
there a little bit stung
少し刺されたような感じですね。
Okay, over to you!
はい、どうぞ！